A Guide to the State Treasurer's Correspondence of the Virginia Dept. of the Treasury, 1962-2022
Library of Virginia
- State Treasurer's correspondence, 1962-1999.
  - Susan F. Dewey - SNAP User's Conference, 1996. (Box 15)
  - VCBA Pricing at Lehman Brothers, 1996. (Box 15)
  - Virginia Executive Insitute Alumni Association, 1996. (Box 15)
  - NAUPA, 1996. (Box 15)
  - Grants Municipal Bond Fall Conference, 1996. (Box 15)
  - Treasury Staff Retreat, 1996. (Box 15)
  - National Institute for Public Conference, 1995. (Box 15)
  - Mid-West Treasurers' Conference, 1996. (Box 15)
  - Strategic Planning meeting, 1996. (Box 15)
  - Joint Subcommittee Bonded Debt, 1996. (Box 15)
  - NAST Annual Meeting, 1995. (Box 15)
  - Susan F. Dewey - Travel, 1996. (Box 15)
  - Council of State Government, 1998. (Box 15)
  - NAST Executive Committee meeting, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Association of Government Accountants, 1998. (Box 15)
  - NASACT - Annual Conference, 1998. (Box 15)
  - NAST - Issues Conference, 1998. (Box 15)
  - NAST - Unclaimed Property, 1998. (Box 15)
  - RFP Selection Panel - Tax Dept., 1998. (Box 15)
  - NASACT - Atlanta, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Institutional Capital Investing, 1998. (Box 15)
  - State Debt Management Network, 1998. (Box 15)
  - National Association of Treasurers, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Southern Treasurers Conference, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Virginia Executive Institute Alumni Association Committee, 1998. (Box 15)
  - SNAP User Conference - Susan Dewey, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Senior Management Retreat, 1998. (Box 15)
  - NAUPA Mid-Year, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Treasury Management, 1998. (Box 15)
  - VPSA Bond Sale, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Hampton Roads Treasury Management, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Virginia Sales and Use Tax, 1998. (Box 15)
  - NAST Legislative Conference, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Bond Buyer - Southeast Public Finance, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Arthur N. Bowen, III - Travel, 1998. (Box 15)
  - SNAP Users Conference - Bowen, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Southern Treasurers Conference, 1998. (Box 15)
  - J. Braxton Powell - NAST Annual meeting, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Arthur N. Bowen, III - Institutional Capital Investing, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Virginia Executive Institute Alumni Association Fall Conference, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Arthur N. Bowen, III - GFOA, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Arthur N. Bowen, III - NAUPA, 1998 Aug-Sept. (Box 15)
  - The Bond Club, 1998 June. (Box 15)
  - Virginia Bond Club, 1998. (Box 15)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1998 Dec. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1998 Nov. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1998 Oct. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1998 Sept. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1998 Aug. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1998 July. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1998 June. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority salary survey, 1997. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board Financing Overview, 1999. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1999 Jan. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1999 Feb. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1999 Mar. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1999 Apr. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1999 May. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1999 June. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1999 July. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1999 Aug. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1999 Sept. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority reports, 1999. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority budget, 1999. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1999 Oct. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1999 Nov. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority - Changes to 2000 Law Income Tax Credit Plan, 1999. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board meeting, 1999 Dec. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority - General, 1999. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority - Correspondence, 1997-1998. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority - General, 1995-1996. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority - Single Family, 1994-1995. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority - Legislative Committee, 1995. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority - Overview, 1990-1992. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority - Comments received January 19-22 on Amendement to Single Family Rules and Regulations, 1996. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority - Expense forms, 1993-1996. (Box 18)
  - NCSHA Legislative Conference, 1996. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority - Audit Committee, 1996. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority - Housing Partnership Fund, 1995. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority - Multi-Family, 1997. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority - Single Family, 1997. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority Board Retreat, 1996. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Public School Authority, 1997 Sept-1998 July. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Public School Authority, 1995 Sept-1997 Aug. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Public School Authority - Correspondence, 1996-1998. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Public School Authority, 1999. (Box 18)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Resolution ratings, 1997. (Box 18)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board package, 1996 Sept. (Box 18)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board package, 1997 Feb. (Box 19)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board package, 1997 June. (Box 19)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board package, 1997 Aug. (Box 19)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board package, 1997 Sept. (Box 19)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board package, 1997 Oct. (Box 19)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board package, 1998 Mar. (Box 19)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board package, 1998 July. (Box 19)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board package, 1998 Oct. (Box 19)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board package, 1999 Mar. (Box 19)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board minutes, 1962 Oct-1971 Aug. (Box 20)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board minutes, 1972 July-1977 Mar. (Box 20)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board minutes, 1977 Oct-1986 Oct. (Box 20)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board minutes, 1987 Feb-1991 Mar. (Box 20)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board minutes, 1991 May-1992 Dec. (Box 20)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board minutes, 1993 Feb-Apr. (Box 20)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board minutes, 1993 Apr. (Box 20)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board minutes, 1993 May-1994 Apr. (Box 20)
  - Virgnia Public School Authority - Board minutes, 1994 June-1995 July. (Box 20)
  - Virgnia College Building Authority - Board minutes, 1972 Dec-1976 May. (Box 21)
  - Virgnia College Building Authority - Board minutes, 1977 Mar-1985 Feb. (Box 21)
  - Virgnia College Building Authority - Board minutes, 1986 Jan-1989 June. (Box 21)
  - Virgnia College Building Authority - Board minutes, 1990 Jan-1991 June. (Box 21)
  - Virgnia College Building Authority - Board minutes, 1991 Aug-1992 May. (Box 21)
  - Virgnia College Building Authority - Board minutes, 1992 June-1993 Apr. (Box 21)
  - Virgnia College Building Authority - Board minutes, 1993 May-Oct. (Box 21)
  - Virgnia College Building Authority - Correspondence, 1993-1996. (Box 21)
  - Virgnia College Building Authority - Pooled Bond Program, 1996. (Box 21)
  - Virginia Resources Authority - Correspondence, 1998-1999. (Box 22)
  - Virginia Resources Authority - Correspondence, 1996-1998. (Box 22)
  - Virginia Resources Authority - Board meeting, 1999 June. (Box 22)
  - Virginia Resources Authority - Board meeting, 1999 May. (Box 22)
  - Virginia Resources Authority - Board meeting, 1999 Apr. (Box 22)
  - Virginia Resources Authority - Board meeting, 1999 Mar. (Box 22)
  - Virginia Resources Authority - Board meeting, 1999 Jan. (Box 22)
  - Virginia Resources Authority - Board meeting, 1998 Dec. (Box 22)
  - Virginia Resources Authority - Board meeting, 1998 Oct. (Box 22)
  - Virginia Resources Authority - Employee Handbook, 1998. (Box 22)
  - Virginia Resources Authority - Board meeting, 1998 Aug. (Box 22)
  - Virginia Resources Authority - Board meeting, 1998 July. (Box 22)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1974 Jan-1978 May. (Box 22)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1979 Jan-1981 June. (Box 22)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1981 Aug-1982 Sept. (Box 22)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1982 Oct-1983 Oct. (Box 22)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1983 Nov-1984 Dec. (Box 23)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1985 Jan-1986 June. (Box 23)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1986 July-1987 Nov. (Box 23)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1987 Feb. (Box 23)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1987 Dec-1988 July. (Box 23)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1988 Aug-1989 Apr. (Box 23)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1989 May-1990 Aug. (Box 23)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1990 Sept-1991 Dec. (Box 23)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1992 Jan-Oct. (Box 23)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1992 Nov-1993 Mar. (Box 23)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1993 Apr-May. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1993 June-July. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1993 Aug-Sept. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1993 Oct-Nov. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1993 Dec. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1994 Jan-Mar. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1994 Apr-July. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1994 Aug-Nov. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1994 Dec. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1995 Jan-Feb. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1995 Mar-May. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1995 June-Aug. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1995 Sept-Oct. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1995 Nov-Dec. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1996 Jan-Apr. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1996 May-June. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1996 July-Dec. (Box 24)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1997 Jan-June. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1997 July-Dec. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1998 Jan-June. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Minutes, 1998 July-Dec. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Member Orientation, 1994. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1997 Jan. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1997 Feb. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1997 Mar. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1997 Apr. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1997 May. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1997 June. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1997 July. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1997 Aug. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1997 Sept. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1997 Oct. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1997 Nov. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1997 Dec. (Box 25)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1998 Jan. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1998 Feb. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1998 Mar. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1998 Apr. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1998 May. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1998 June. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1998 July. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1998 Aug. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1998 Sept. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1998 Oct. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1998 Nov. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1998 Dec. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1999 Jan. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1999 Feb. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1999 Mar. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1999 Apr. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1999 May. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1999 June. (Box 26)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1999 July. (Box 27)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1999 Aug. (Box 27)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1999 Sept. (Box 27)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1999 Oct. (Box 27)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1999 Nov. (Box 27)
  - Treasury Board - Meeting, 1999 Dec. (Box 27)
  - Treasury Board - Correspondence, 1992. (Box 27)
  - Treasury Board - Correspondence, 1993. (Box 27)
  - Treasury Board - Correspondence, 1994. (Box 27)
  - Treasury Board - Correspondence, 1995. (Box 27)
  - Treasury Board - Correspondence, 1996. (Box 27)
  - Treasury Board - Correspondence, 1997. (Box 27)
  - Treasury Board - Correspondence, 1998. (Box 27)
  - Debt Capacity Advisory Committee update, 1998-1999. (Box 27)
  - Debt Capacity Advisory Committee update, 1994-1997. (Box 27)
  - Debt Capacity Advisorty Committee - House Document No. 50, 1998. (Box 27)
  - Debt Capacity Advisorty Committee - Moratorium on Debt, 1996. (Box 27)
  - Debt Capacity Advisorty Committee meeting, 1997 Dec. (Box 27)
  - Debt Capacity Advisorty Committee meeting, 1997 Sept. (Box 27)
  - Debt Capacity Advisorty Committee presentation, 1997 Jan. (Box 27)
  - Debt Capacity Advisorty Committee, 1997. (Box 27)
  - Debt Capacity Advisorty Committee, 1996. (Box 27)
  - Debt Capacity Advisorty Committee, 1995. (Box 27)
  - VADA, 1988-1995. (Box 27)
  - Assistive Technology Loan Fund Authority meeting, 1999 Apr. (Box 27)
  - Assistive Technology Loan Fund Authority, 1997-1999. (Box 27)
  - Assistive Technology Loan Fund Authority meeting, 1997 Jan. (Box 27)
  - Assistive Technology Loan Authority meeting, 1995 Dec. (Box 27)
  - Virginia College Building Authority - Correspondence, 1999. (Box 28)
  - Virginia College Building Authority - Correspondence, 1993-1995. (Box 28)
  - Virginia College Building Authority - Correspondence, 1996-1998. (Box 28)
  - Virginia College Building Authority - University of Richmond, 1996. (Box 28)
  - Virginia College Building Authority - Board meeting, 1996 Apr. (Box 28)
  - Virginia College Building Authority - Board meeting, 1996 July. (Box 28)
  - Virginia College Building Authority - Board meeting, 1996 Sept. (Box 28)
  - Virginia College Building Authority - Board meeting, 1996 Oct. (Box 28)
  - Virginia College Building Authority - Board meeting, 1997 Apr. (Box 28)
  - Virginia College Building Authority - Board meeting, 1997 Aug. (Box 28)
  - Virginia College Building Authority - Board meeting, 1997 Nov. (Box 28)
  - Virginia College Building Authority - Board meeting, 1998 Mar. (Box 28)
  - Virginia College Building Authority - Board meeting, 1998 Aug. (Box 28)
  - Virginia College Building Authority - Board meeting, 1998 Dec. (Box 28)
  - Virginia College Building Authority - Board meeting, 1999 Apr. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Correspondence, 1995. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Correspondence, 1996. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Correspondence, 1997. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Correspondence, 1998. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Correspondence, 1999. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Bear Stearns presentation, 1996 May. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Board meeting, 1997 Jan. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Board meeting, 1997 Mar. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Board meeting, 1997 Apr. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Board meeting, 1997 Sept. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Board meeting, 1997 Nov. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Board meeting, 1998 Feb. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Board meeting, 1998 May. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Board meeting, 1998 Dec. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Board meeting, 1999 Apr. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority - Audits, 1999. (Box 29)
  - State Council on Local Debt - Minutes, 1985 Jan-1991 Dec. (Box 29)
  - State Council on Local Debt - Minutes, 1993 Apr-Oct. (Box 29)
  - State Council on Local Debt - Minutes, 1992 Jan-1994 Apr. (Box 29)
  - State Council on Local Debt - Minutes, 1993 Nov-1995 Apr. (Box 29)
  - State Council on Local Debt - Minutes, 1995 June-1996 Apr. (Box 29)
  - Ronald Tillet - Conflict of interest, 1995. (Box 30)
  - Conflict of interest, 1995. (Box 30)
  - Maclin Whiteman, 1994. (Box 30)
  - Belinda Blanchard, 1995. (Box 30)
  - Judy Siler, 1997. (Box 30)
  - Laurie Westberry, 1995. (Box 30)
  - Capitol Police (restricted), 1999. (Box 30)
  - Susan Dewey, 1993-1999. (Box 30)
  - Susan Dewey - Bio, 1996-1998. (Box 30)
  - Susan Dewey - NAST profile, 1999. (Box 30)
  - Higher Education Tuition Trust Fun - Executive Director, 1996. (Box 30)
  - Ronald Tillet - Bio, 1996. (Box 30)
  - Letter to the Editor, 1995. (Box 30)
  - Susan Dewey - Photographs, 1997. (Box 30)
  - News clippings, 1996-1997. (Box 30)
  - News clippings - Susan Dewey, 1995-1999. (Box 30)
  - Treasury Dept. - Newspaper articles, 1990-1993. (Box 30)
  - Treasury Dept. - Newspaper articles, 1980-1991. (Box 30)
  - State agency heads listing, 1997. (Box 30)
  - Board attendance roster, 1992-1997. (Box 30)
  - James Monroe conference rooms, 1996-1997. (Box 30)
  - Travel, 1994-1997. (Box 30)
  - Board candidates, 1992-1997. (Box 30)
  - Investment guidelines, 1996. (Box 30)
  - Garnishment, 1996. (Box 30)
  - Treasury Board appointment, 1993. (Box 30)
  - NAST News Tip Sheet, 1991. (Box 30)
  - Records management, 1998. (Box 30)
  - Freedom of information, 1994. (Box 30)
  - Media alerts to the Governor's Office, 1988-1999. (Box 30)
  - General obligation bonds - House Appropriations, 1997. (Box 30)
  - The Bond Club of Virginia, 1997. (Box 30)
  - Dept Capacity Advisory Committee, 1996. (Box 30)
  - Grants Municipal Board, 1996. (Box 30)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Debt and Debt Capacity, 1996. (Box 30)
  - VCBA Pooled Bond Program, 1996. (Box 30)
  - Financial Women International, 1996. (Box 30)
  - Financial Management Issues - Society of Municipal Analysis, 1996. (Box 30)
  - Lithuania Delegation, 1996. (Box 30)
  - Presentation to The Bond Club of Virginia, 1996. (Box 30)
  - Senate Finance Committee - Virginia's Prepaid Tuition Program, 1996. (Box 30)
  - Legg Mason Public Finance Roundable, 1995. (Box 30)
  - Annual SNAP User's Conference, 1995. (Box 30)
  - Flat Tax - Speech information, undated. (Box 30)
  - Public Finance Roundtable - Legg Mason, 1995. (Box 30)
  - The Best Bet on Developing a Savings Plan, 1995. (Box 30)
  - Performance Management for Public Funds (S and P), 1995. (Box 30)
  - Presentation to the Office of the Governor and Secretary of Finance, 1995. (Box 31)
  - Secondary Market disclosure - Presentation to The Bond Club of Virginia, 1995. (Box 31)
  - Chinese Delegation - Susan Dewey, 1995. (Box 31)
  - State Internal Auditor, 1996-1998. (Box 31)
  - State Police, Dept. of, 1994-1998. (Box 31)
  - Taxation, Dept. of, 1992-1999. (Box 31)
  - Transportation, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 31)
  - Transportation, Dept. of - 895 Connector, 1998. (Box 31)
  - Virginia Center for Innovative Technology, 1994-1996. (Box 31)
  - Virginia Code Commission, 1992-1997. (Box 31)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, 1992-1997. (Box 31)
  - Virginia Liaison Office, 1993-1994. (Box 31)
  - Virginia Retirement System, 1992-1998. (Box 31)
  - Visually Handicapped, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 31)
  - Volunteerism, Dept. of, 1987-1994. (Box 31)
  - Youth and Family Services, Dept. of, 1993-1995. (Box 31)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1993-1999. (Box 31)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Audit comment, 1998-1999. (Box 31)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Revenue Stabilization Fund, 1997-1998. (Box 31)
  - Attorney General's Office - Notice of Service Transmittal, 1997-1998. (Box 31)
  - Money Committee staff, 1997-1999. (Box 31)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1998. (Box 31)
  - Legislative Services, 1997. (Box 31)
  - Correspondence - Senators and Delegates, 1999. (Box 31)
  - Christopher Newport College, 1992-1998. (Box 31)
  - George Mason University, 1991-1999. (Box 31)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia, 1996-1997. (Box 31)
  - Commonwealth Health Research Board, 1997. (Box 31)
  - Norfolk State University, 1990-1998. (Box 31)
  - Old Dominion University, 1990. (Box 31)
  - University of Virginia, 1992-1999. (Box 31)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1992-1998. (Box 31)
  - Virginia State University, 1992-1999. (Box 31)
  - Universities - General, 1996-1997. (Box 31)
  - Secretary of Finance, 1999. (Box 31)
  - Secretary of Finance, 1998. (Box 31)
  - Secretary of Finance, 1997. (Box 31)
  - Secretary of Finance, 1996. (Box 31)
  - Dept. of Accounts / Dept. of Planning and Budget - Study of Non-General Funds (Centralized Payroll), 1994-1995. (Box 32)
  - Federal legislation issues, 1994. (Box 32)
  - Secretary of Finance - School construction, 1998. (Box 32)
  - Finance Agency Heads - Retreat, 1996. (Box 32)
  - Finance Secretariat - Strategic Plan, 1997. (Box 32)
  - Secretary of Finance - Studies/Projects, 1998. (Box 32)
  - Finance Agency Heads, 1997. (Box 32)
  - Finance Workshops, 1997. (Box 32)
  - Finance Agency Heads, 1996. (Box 32)
  - Finance Agency Heads - Retreat, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Finance Agency Heads, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Finance Agency Heads, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Presentations to the General Assembly, 1993-1996. (Box 32)
  - Overview of Gov. Gilmore's Budget Actions, 1998-2000. (Box 32)
  - Privatization Proposals - Finance Agency Heads recommendations, 1994. (Box 32)
  - Agency Heads, 1992-1998. (Box 32)
  - Public-Private Partnership in Transportation, 1995. (Box 32)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1992-1999. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Economic Development, 1992-1997. (Box 32)
  - Venture Capital and Business Start-Up, 1994. (Box 32)
  - Secretary of Education, 1994-1997. (Box 32)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1993. (Box 32)
  - Secretary of Technology, 1999. (Box 32)
  - Dept. of Accounts, 1996-1999. (Box 32)
  - Agriculture and Consumer Services, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 32)
  - Air and Space Museum, 1993-1998. (Box 32)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of, 1992-1993. (Box 32)
  - Aviation, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 32)
  - Compensation Board, 1997. (Box 32)
  - Commission on Local Government, 1996-1999. (Box 32)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 32)
  - Commonwealth Competition Council, 1995-1998. (Box 32)
  - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 1994-1998. (Box 32)
  - Council on Information Development, 1992-1998. (Box 32)
  - Criminal Justice, Dept. of, 1995-1997. (Box 32)
  - Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992-1997. (Box 32)
  - Education, Dept. of, 1992-1998. (Box 32)
  - Emergency Services, Dept. of, 1995-1997. (Box 32)
  - Employee Relations Counselors, 1993-1997. (Box 32)
  - Environmental Quality, Dept. of, 1998. (Box 32)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 32)
  - General Services, Dept. of (Purchase and Supply), 1992-1999. (Box 32)
  - Governor's Employment and Training Dept., 1995. (Box 32)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1990-1995. (Box 32)
  - Information Technology, Dept. of, 1993-1998. (Box 32)
  - Joint Committee on Healthcare, 1993. (Box 32)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC), 1992-1995. (Box 32)
  - Legislative Services, Dept. of, 1992-1996. (Box 32)
  - Library of Virginia, 1993-1998. (Box 32)
  - Lottery, Dept. of, 1992-1998. (Box 32)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 32)
  - Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of, 1993-1997. (Box 32)
  - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1993-1994. (Box 32)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1994-1998. (Box 32)